Mike North: 这是我们的数组示例。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Here's our array example.
索引签名看起来像这里，方括号，有意义的权利。
Index signatures which look like this
here, square brackets, makes sense right.
因为这就是我们使用任意键访问对象的属性的方式。
Because that's how we access a property
off of an object with an arbitrary key.
我们说，如果你访问一个电话号码字典的属性，并给它一个字符串。
We are saying if you access a property off
a phone number dict and give it a string.
它要么根本不存在，要么就会有这个表格。
It'll either not be there at all,
or it'll have this form.
现在，当您定义这样的字典类型时,
Now, when you are defining
a dictionary type like this, and
字典只是一个键值数据结构,
a dictionary is just a key
value data structure,
几乎可以肯定，你以前用过一个物体作为字典
you have almost certainly used
an object as a dictionary before in
属性键具有一致的对象类型，对。
JavaScript property keys with
consistent object types, right.
你必须小心，不要以打字稿的方式输入
You've got to be careful that you don't
type this in such a way that TypeScript
给你一个虚假的保证，不管你传入什么属性键,
gives you a false guarantee that no
matter what property key you pass in,
你肯定会得到一个明确的值。
you will definitely get
a well-defined value out.
让我们看看如果我们这样做会发生什么。
Let's look at what would
happen if we did that.
迈克 · 诺斯: 那么，一个空的物体在这里就是一个有效的例子，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So, an empty object
is a valid case here, right?
没有钥匙，不管我做什么，都是在演戏
No keys, and
no matter what I do it's acting
好像有什么是属于我的。
like there's something there for me.
这是一个很难跟踪错误等待发生，所以不要这样做。
This is a hard to track down error
waiting to happen, so don't do that.
通过添加未定义的，Mike North: 我们强迫,
By adding undefined,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: We force,
迈克 · 诺斯: 检查一下这个
&gt;&gt; Mike North: A check on this, and
你要做的就是这样。
what you'd have to do
is something like this.
迈克 · 诺斯: 看到这里的未定义是什么了吗？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: See how up here
the undefined is present?
并且在条件之后的块中，未定义的内容已经消失。
And inside the block following the
condition the undefined has disappeared.
我们在这里所做的是缩小类型。
What we have done here
is narrowed the type.
明白这个条件，它明白
TypeScript understands that this
condition that it understands that
这种人永远不会有真正的价值，永远。
this type here can never
have a truthy value, never.
因此，未定义的值不可能传递到这个块中。
So, there is no way for an undefined
value to pass into this block here.
而这正是我们想要的正确用途。
And this is the proper use
that we would want anyway.
因为如果我们只是接到一些
Because if we're just handed something and
我们被告知这种类型的，我们不一定知道里面有什么。
we're told that it's this type we don't
necessarily know what's on there.
我们不知道哪些按键对于查找信息是有效的。
We don't know which keys are valid for
looking things up.
因此，条件可以用来缩小类型。
So, conditions can be
used to narrow types.
我们可以用不同的方法。
We could do it a different way.
迈克 · 诺斯: 恰恰相反，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: It's just the inverse,
right?
我们正在检查 d.abc 的类型是否是一个对象。
We're checking to see if
the type of d.abc is an object.
迈克 · 诺斯: 让我们看看这个会发生什么，不可能。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Let's see what
happens with this, impossible.
它说这就像是文恩图表打字稿总是试图
It says this is like in terms of the Venn
diagram TypeScript's always trying to
想办法解决问题。
figure out a way to make things work.
这种情况下它会说好吧,
This is a situation
where it's saying okay,
它可以是未定义的，也可以是一个对象。
this can either be undefined or an object.
现在我们有了一些代码，在字符串的情况下可以运行。
So now we have some code that would
run in the case where it's a string.
永远不会发生，所以你永远不会。
Never gonna happen never,
so you get never.
我把它放在那儿，你可以继续查。
I'll leave that there so
you can follow on that.
好的，这是我们的电话号码字典。
Okay, here is our phone number dictionary.
这就证明了我们可以在这里放置价值观
And this is just demonstrating
that we can place values in there
如果我们拼错了什么，我们会被逮到的，对吧。
if we misspelt something we'd
get busted on it, right.
它告诉我们没有 araCode，我们必须把它拼对，araCode。
It's telling us there's no araCode,
we have to spell that right, areaCode.
我马上就试着剪辑一下，不过还是看看现在会发生什么吧。
I'm gonna try editing it in a second, but
let's just see what happens right now.
所以，我们可以消除它，因为如果这是在我们的手机通讯录页面,
So, we can eliminate it because if this
were in our contacts page in our phone,
那里可能有多个电话号码。
we could have multiple
phone numbers there.
有些人没有家庭电话号码,
Some people are not gonna
have a home number,
他们只有一个办公室电话，所以，没关系。
they'll only have an office number,
so, this is fine.
所以它看起来像这些值的结构，这是强制的。
So it look likes the structure of
these values here, that's enforced.
但是我们可以完全控制键的属性。
But we have total control over
what the properties keys are.
有一点很重要，那就是您最多只能有一个字符串
One thing that's important to know is
that you can only have at most one string
索引签名和一个数字索引签名。
index signature and
one number index signature.
所以，你可以把这个改成喜欢的数字，然后得到一些稍微不同于
So, you could change this to like number
and have something slightly different than
如果你传入一个字符串，并试图以这种方式访问一个属性。
if you passed a string in and
tried to access a property that way.